<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Jeremy Olliffe</title><link>https://jolliff3.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Jeremy Olliffe</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jolliff3.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reflection 1 - Principles of sustainability to create viable systems</title><link>https://jolliff3.github.io/posts/reflection1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jolliff3.github.io/posts/reflection1/</guid><description>About halfway through my internship, I was tasked with exploring ways that the company could minimise their energy costs while continuing to meet sustainability requirements. As the company I work for primarily sells energy to electric vehicle drivers, I realised this would have a large impact on the company’s overall profitability. I was excited to undertake such a big and important task. The specific task I was given was open-ended: “minimise cost of goods without breaking our sustainability contracts”.</description></item><item><title>Reflection 2 - Professional Practice within Intercultural and Global Contexts</title><link>https://jolliff3.github.io/posts/reflection2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jolliff3.github.io/posts/reflection2/</guid><description>Each week at work, one person or team will give a presentation to the rest of the workplace with the goal of knowledge sharing and education. One week, one team member gave a presentation on a recent business trip to Europe where they engaged with other electric vehicle charging companies. This presentation focused on three delivery companies and how policies in Europe had encouraged a quicker adoption of Electric vehicles then otherwise would have been feasible.</description></item></channel></rss>